{
    "id": "dd16dff108ca4a45b01bfdc66259bb90",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He ……………… from Malaysia yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has returned",
                "returned",
                "had returned"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c1b2c303b8f84ecc96b3c782da2c3065"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………….. you know where he lives?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Has",
                "Have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1125837c3fbc48baa8e9cdf5cc6fa57b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ........................ what she was supposed to do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did not know",
                "does not know",
                "has not known"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b2b65dde715e4c45b1c1bf94db764c93"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. for my keys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "look",
                "am looking",
                "have looked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d3d857a24c674a92969f1fbbe6a56bf4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… for his exams.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "prepare",
                "prepares",
                "is preparing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "14ba1ec12ae144f9b11c80d77865abea"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………. to be an engineer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is wanting",
                "wants",
                "want"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43e4287375304b27b14ca83815e0227f"
        },
        {
            "question": "God ………………… the stars and the sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is ruling",
                "rules",
                "has ruled"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "43a20e90f18b47999411dfb016f8d9e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two brothers ………………….. each other warmly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "embrace",
                "embraced",
                "has embraced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5571ea4263d944c59b2be6ae9ecf7c88"
        },
        {
            "question": "Next morning, she ………………. up early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "got",
                "gets",
                "was getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a700d2916ce44b4fb5e30431c81a0921"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are you ………………. there?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "doing",
                "done"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cba570ee72664d46ae269c77a27a488e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. him for several years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "know",
                "knew",
                "have known"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "632fca0db685415fa6fbf3b701b719d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. he know what he is doing?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "42d2bc1de6cf43ce81e55f6509358ae9"
        },
        {
            "question": "As he was not willing to accept our help, we ………………. (leave) him to his fate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "were leaving",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8fd8d5e040204f7f8eee1b8ef67155c6"
        }
    ]
}